-You're always sick. -You were sick when you were my age.
-你总是生病 -你像我这么大时也一样
-Evening, sir. -Evening, Victor.
-晚安' 先生 -晚安，维克多
I didn't realize you were still here.
我没想到你还在这儿
I was just keeping James company, sir, if that's all right.
我只是想陪陪他，如果可以的话
Very kind of you.
你真好
-Any better, Son? -Still cold, Father.
-好点了吗， 儿子 ? -还是觉得冷，父亲
Just a mild fever.
就是有点发烧
-You'll be all right in the morning. -You always say that.
-早上就好了 -你总是这么说
And you always pull through, don't you?
你总能恢复
-Yeah. -Now, you taking your medicine?
-对 -吃药了吗 ?
Elizabeth! Elizabeth!
伊丽落白 !
-Your father's drunk again. -Elizabeth!
-你莹葡又喝多了 -伊丽莎白 !
-You should help him home, Victor. -It's not my name he's calling, sir.
-带他回家， 维克多 -他喊的不是我， 先生
-Father! -Stay where you are, James.
-区和爸 ! -待着别动， 詹姆斯
-Get off me! -Father!
-让开 ! -区和爸 !
Now! You never loved him!
现在就跟我走 ! 你从没爱过他 !
I told you never to come back here.
我跟你说过别再回来
Get out!
滚出去 !
James?
詹姆斯
-No. -James?
-不 -舱姆斯
-There are things you don't understand. -Don't.
-你不明白 -别
-l need him to know! -Please don't.
-他应该知道 -别这样
-No more lies. -James...
-不要再骗他了
-No! -James!
-不! -詹姆斯 !
He... He wasn't your father,
他不是你爸葡
Son.
儿子
What are you?
你是什么 ?
-I didn't mean it! 1 didn't mean it! -Yes, you did!
-我不是故意的 ! -不，你是故意的 !
He deserved it, and you gave it to him.
他自找的，你做的没错
We're brothers, Jimmy. You realize that?
我们是亲兄弟，吉米，你明白了吗 ?
And brothers protect each other.
亲兄弟互相保护
You have to be hard now, hard so nothing can ever touch us.
一定要狠，谁也别想欺负我们
-l want to go home. -We can't.
-我想回家 -我们回不去了
We stick together, no matter what,
我们只能相依为命
and take care of anyone who gets in our way.
谁挡我们的路，就叫他好看
Can you do that, little brother?
你能做到吗，弟弟 ?
-I'm going down to the river. -They're coming.
-我去河那边 -他们过来了
-Head over the hill. Hurry! -Can you run?
-往山上跑 , 快! -你能跑吗 ?
-Keep on running and don't look back. -Okay.
-一直跑，别回头 -好
Back to back!
背靠背 !
That's enough!
够了 !
No! No!
不1!
Stand down, soldier!
停下' 士兵 !
Victor!
维克多 !
Stand down! Stand down!
味下!
No!
不1!
Ready, aim...
预备，瞄准…
Wake me when it's over.
完事了叫醒我
.. fire!
…开火!
Freaks! You're animals! Freaks!
怪物 ! 你们是野兽 ! 怪物 !
My name is Major William Stryker.
我是威廉史崔克少校
You've been charged with killing a senior officer.
你们被控杀死长官
Is that correct?
没铭枉你们吧 ?
Apparently, we have some issues with authority...
我们对当权者不满…
-Just keep a lid on it. - -...SIP.
-闭嘴
The warden tells me that your sentence was carried out by a firing squad
监狱长说你们的死刑已经在
at 1000 hours.
上午1 0点进行
-How'd that go? -It tickled.
-怎么回事 ? -简直就是挠痒痒
You boys tired of running? Tired of denying your true nature?
你们不想再跑了 ? 不想再隐瞒你们的本性了 ?
-What do you care? -Oh, I care.
-你会在意我们吗 ? -我在意
I care because I know how special you are.
因为我知道你们与众不同
How valuable.
是有用之才
Look, you can stay here locked up like freaks of nature,
与其像怪物一样被锁在这里
so or you can join me.
还不如跟我二
I'm putting together a special team with special privileges.
我在组织一个有特权的特别行动小组
Now, tell me, how would you like to really serve your country?
告诉我，愿意为祖国效劳吗 ?
You know, I love this weapon
这是我的挚爱
more than any other thing in the whole wide world.
世上任何东西都没法比
-Do you wanna know why? -No.
-想知道为什么吗 ? -不
It's memorable.
它很有纪念意义
Sure, it's a little bulky, tough to get on a plane.
的确，把它带上飞机是有点难
You whip out a couple of swords at your ex-girlfriend's wedding,
要是在前女友婚礼上拔出剑来
they will never, ever forget it.
谁都不会忘记的
That's funny, Wade.
真有趣，韦德
I think you confuse me with someone who gives a shit.
你让一个不相干的人把我弄糊涂了
Right, it's probably not as intimidating as having a gun
剑是比不上枪
or bone claws or the fingernails of a bag lady.
或者爪子 ' 或拾破烂女人的尖指甲
-Manicure? -Victor. Easy.
-想修指甲吗 ? -维克多，别冲动
Fred got a new tattoo. I'm concerned.
弗菜德弄了个新纹身，我担心
Oh, Jesus, Fred, you just met her last night.
天啊，你和她昨晚刚认识
-l love her. -You love her after one night?
-我爱她 -就一晚上就爱上了 ?
She's a gymnast.
她可是体操运动员
Bradley, take her down.
布莱德利降落吧
Oh, God.
哦，上帝
-Are you gonna puke? -lf we were meant to fly,
-你想吐吗 ? -如果你想飞
-we'd grow wings. -Don't worry, Nancy.
-得先长出翅膀啊 -别担心，大姐
-More people die driving than flying. -How about from impaling?
-死于车祸的人比死于飞机失事的多 -那死于钢爪下的人呢 ?
Hey, be nice, or be your approximation of nice.
要友善，或者尽可能友善
-Would you like a bucket? -No.
-要个桶吗 ? -不
Gentlemen, wheels down in Lagos in five.
先生们“， 五分钟后降落
-Why are we here? -All in good time. Zero?
-我们来这于什么 ? -你会知道的，零号 ?
-Intruder! Perimeter breach! -Man the weapon!
-有人入侵 ! 外围遇次 ! -准备武器 !
Intruder, stop! Put your hands behind your head!
入侵者，不许动 ! 把手放头上 !
Having fun yet?
不来玩玩吗 ?
-Fred? -The tank?
-弗菜德 ? -坦克 ?
-The tank. -Yeah, I got that.
-是的 -好的，我来
Great. Stuck in an elevator with five guys on a high-protein diet.
真棒，五壮汉挤一个电梯
-Wade. -Dreams really do come true.
-直德 -美梦成真啊
Just shut it!
闭嘴 !
-You're up next. -Thank you, sir. You look really nice today.
-下一个就是你 -谢谢长官， 你今天气色不错
It's the green. It brings out the seriousness in your eyes.
绿色灯光让你的眼神更显严肃
-Oh, my God. Do you ever shut up, pal? -No. Not when I'm awake.
-你嘴巴能不能闭上，伙计 ? -不能，除非我睡着了
Bradley? Top floor, please.
布菜德利，到顶层
Cover the elevator! The elevator!
集中瞄准电梯 !
Time to go to work.
该开工了
Okay. People are dead.
好了，人全挂了
If you didn't have that mouth on you, Wade, you'd be the perfect soldier.
要是没那张嘴，你就完美了
I wouldn't do that if 1 was you, brother.
我要是你就不会开火
-Take the diamonds. They're yours. -l don't want your diamonds.
-拿走钻石，都是你们的 -我不要钻石
I want this.
我要的是这个
But that is nothing. A souvenir.
那一文不值，就是个纪念品
Where did you find it? l want the source.
我想知道你从哪儿得来的
A small village, far inland, three days from here.
内陆的一个小村子，离这里三天行程
Tell him this rock is more valuable to me than his life.
告诉他这石头比他命值钱
Ask him where he found it.
问他哪儿找到的
Okay.
好
He says it came from the sky.
他说从天上掉下来的
He's telling the truth.
他说的是实话
You don't know the language, Logan.
你连他说什么都不懂，罗根
-It's a meteor fragment. -l know what it is.
-那是块陨石碎片 -我知道
I'm asking him where he found it.
我想问他哪儿捡的
Sir, base wants to know our location.
长官，基地想知道我们的位置
-Shut them down. -Yes.
-别理它 -是
Tell him everyone here will die
告诉他，他们统统得死
unless he tells me where he found the rock.
如果他不说在哪儿的话
-He says that it's sacred. -Okay, fine.
-他说那是圣物 -那好吧
Victor.
维克多
Victor!
维克多 !
Don't even think about it.
杀了他，想都别想
We didn't sign up for this.
我们可不是来杀人的
Put him down!
松开他 !
What are you doing?
你怎么了 ?
We finally got a good thing going here. Don't you screw this up.
终于有人收留我们' 别搞磺了
Enough. That's enough. We've done enough.
我们做的够多了
Who do you think you are?
你以为你是谁 ?
This is what we do.
我们就是于这个的
Maybe you'd rather be rotting in a hole somewhere
你是不是宁愿在他们于掉我们前
till they figure out a way to do it to us. Is that it? Huh?
找个洞躲起来烂掉 ?
I'm done.
我受够了
You coming?
你跟我走吗 ?
Jimmy!
吉米 !
We can't just let you walk away.
我们不能让你一走了之
Why are you up so early?
你怎么起这么星 ?
Come here.
过来
See you, baby.
过会儿见，宝页
Hey.
嘿
Oh, that's nice. Yes. Take your time.
哎呀， 真是美
You're wrapped, man.
看来是被收拾了“，你可真服帖
Okay, I'm totally gonna get this.
这次我肯定赢
Nope. Come on.
不可能，走吧
Oh, wow! Let's go on the Ferris wheel.
了哇哦，咱们去坐摩天轮吧
-How does he do it? -Come on.
-他怎么做到的 ? -来吧
..-amazing lady in a box!
…盒子里的美女 !
Swing the hammer, ring the bell!
挥动锤子，敲响铃 !
Hey, what do you do?
路，你是做什么的
If you turn off the light, you win a prize.
只要你能把灯灭了，就能得奖
-Three tries for a buck. -Come on, I wanna do it.
-一块钱三次 -我想玩这个
There you go. Okay?
给你钱
No, that's obvious.
显然地
That's two.
两次了
Well, that's a stupid trick.
骗人的把戏
It's not a trick, man.
才不是呢， 哥们儿
Come on. Freak.
走吧， 怪物
Bye.
慢走
Show's over!
游戏结束了 !
I said show's over!
我说过游戏结束了 !
The show's never over for us, Bradley.
对于我们永远不会结束 布莱德利
-Victor. -Aren't you gonna invite me in?
-维克多 -不想请我进去吗 ?
Yeah. Come on in.
进来吧
You know, I've never said anything to anyone about what happened.
我从来没有向任何人提起过去的事
I'm living a totally different life now, Victor.
我现在过着完全不同的生活
No need to bring up the past.
过去的就让它过去吧
You know,
知道吗
l always thought it would be Wade to come knocking at my door.
我一直以为会是韦德找上门来
Well... Well,
哦
Wade's gone.
韦德已经死了
I'm not afraid of you, Victor.
我可不怕你，维克多
I'm not afraid of dying.
我也不怕死
How do you know?
你怎么知道 ?
You've never tried it before.
你又没试过
Was it the wars?
又梦到打仗了 ?
Which one?
哪一场
All of them.
所有的
-Tell me. -Hey.
-和我说说 -嘿
It's just a scratch.
只是擦破点皮
Looks like we're gonna need new sheets again, baby.
看来我们又得换新床单了
Yeah.
是啊
Who the hell is this?
到底是谁来了 ?
Smells like government.
闻起来像政府官员
My God. Haven't aged a day!
我的天，你一点都没老
Clean living.
清白做人
-You remember Agent Zero? -Still shooting first, asking questions later?
-还记得零号特工吗 ? -他还是先开枪后提问 ?
-You still chewing on cheap cigars? -Boys, please.
-你也还是抽这破雪茄 ? -各位，拜托
-l have a job for you. -l already have a job.
-我有事给你做 -我已经有事做了
Lumberjack? 18 grand a year?
伐木工 ? 一年一万八千块 ?
18.5. Plus I haven't had to kill anyone in a while.
一万八寺五，而且不用杀人
-Starting to miss it? -Right about now I am.
-手痒痒了吗 ? -现在有点
-Yeah? -Zero, back to the car.
-是吗 ? -零号 , 回车上去
Attaboy.
可真氟
You know, I'm not proud about the way things ended between us.
搞的这么伪，我很不自在
Conversation's over.
和你没话说
Playing Little House on the Prairie with a schoolteacher,
和一个老师玩过家家
I mean, that just isn't you, Logan.
那不是你，罗根
And you would know, huh?
这你也知道哈
-l would. -What do you want, Stryker?
-是的 -你想怎样，史峙克 ?
Bradley was killed three days ago.
布莱德利三天前被杀了
Wade before that.
韦德在他之前死了
I believe that someone is hunting down our old team.
有人想把我们这些老队员杀光
-Anyone else? -As far as I know, Victor is safe.
-还有谁被杀了 -据我所知， 维克多还活着
But whoever it is has names, addresses.
有名有姓的人，时了晚会被找到的
I can take care of myself.
我能照顾好自己
This is not about you, Logan.
不光是你，罗根
Your country needs you.
你的国家需要你
I'm Canadian.
我是加拿大人
I know you, Logan! I know who you are!
我了解你，罗根 ! 我知道你是什么人 !
-Miss Kayla, Miss Kayla, look what I did. -What did you do?
-项拉小姐，看我做的 -你做了什么 ?
Bye, Miss Silverfox! Bye!
再见，斯沃福克斯小姐
What's wrong?
怎么了 ?
Stryker came by today.
史崔克今天来找我
Don't worry. I said no.
别担心，我拒绝了
Why is he bothering you after all these years?
这么多年了，怎么还来烦你
Because I'm the best there is at what I do,
因为我于得最漂亮
but what I do best isn't very nice.
但我于得漂亮的事不是好事
You're not an animal, Logan. What you have is a gift.
你不是动物，罗根' 你拥有着天赋
A gift. You can return a gift.
天赋是可以还回去的
Come on, fellas.
快走啊，伙计们
All right.
好了
Stay in the car.
呆在车里
I'm just gonna ask nicely.
我会很礼煞的问
You mind letting us go by?
可以让我们过去吗 ?
-You in some kind of a hurry there, pal? -Hey, hey, hey.
-你有急事吗，朋友 ? -嘿
Are you?
有了吗 ?
Just move your truck so we can go by.
挪下车吧
We're trying to have a conversation there, all right?
我们在聊天
You start something, you'd better be ready to finish it.
你挑起来的，最好你能了结
Hey, guys, take it easy! Calm down.
伙计们，别冲动 ! 冷静点
-Your boyfriend's got a big mouth. -l know.
-你男朋友真多嘴 -我知道
Big temper, too. So please let us pass.
脾气也大，请让我们过去吧
-Thank you. -Come on, man, let's go.
-谢谢你 -我们走肥
How'd you do that?
你怎么搞定的 ?
Female powers of persuasion. It's a gift.
女性的说服力，这是天赋
Oh, I see. Do you have those powers over me?
明白，你那招对我也管用吗 ?
Well, you didn't stay in the car, did you?
你并没有呆在车里，不是吗 ?
Why is the moon so lonely?
月亮为什么这么孤单 ?
Why?
为什么 ?
Because she used to have a lover.
因为她普经有过爱人
-You tell this to the kids? -No.
-你跟孩子们就讲这个 -不
His name was Kuekuatsheu and they lived in the Spirit World together.
他叫库艾酷瓦楚， 他们一起住在仙界
Oh, this is a true story? All right.
哦，还真有其事 ?
And every night they would wander the skies together,
每晚他们都一起在天空漫步
but one of the other spirits was jealous.
结果遭到一个精灵的嫉妒
Trickster wanted the moon for himself,
峙斯特想把月亮女神占为已有
so he told Kuekuatsheu that the moon had asked for flowers.
于是他告诉库艾酷瓦楚，月亮想要花
He told him to come to our world and pick her some wild roses,
他教库艾酷瓦楚下凡来摘野玫现
but Kuekuatsheu didn't know that once you leave the Spirit World,
但库艾酷瓦楚不知道一旦离开仙界
you can never go back.
就再也回不去了
And every night he looks up in the sky and sees the moon and howls her name.
每晚， 他只能仰望月亮呼唤好的名字
But
但是
he can never touch her again.
他们再也无法相拥
Wow.
哇
Koo-koo-ka-choo got screwed.
酷酷卡楚被骗了
“Kuekuatsheu.”
库艾酷瓦楚
It means “the Wolverine”.
是“金刚狼”的意思
What you doing, Logan?
你怎么了，罗根 ?
Kayla.
如拉
Oh, God.
天啊
Kayla!
如拉 !
You're not from around here, are you?
你不是本地人吧 ?
What gave me away?
何以见得 ?
Victor!
维克多 !
-You got insurance on this place? -Insurance? No.
-你这地方上保险了吗 ? -保险 ? 没有
-Too bad. -Victor!
-维克多 !
Well, well, well. Look what the cat dragged in.
瞧瞧，这只猫怎么被拖下水
Guys, whatever this is, take it outside.
兄弟们 ' 不管有什么过节 请外面解决
Why?
为什么 ?
You don't call. You don't write.
你不打电话，不写信
How else am I supposed to get your attention?
那我怎么能让你理我 ?
Il hate to say it, Jimmy, but, frankly, I'm a little disappointed.
我本不想说，吉米 但坦白地说，我有点失望
Stay down.
冷静
Tell me something, Jimmy. Was she worth it?
告诉我，吉米，她值得你这样吗 ?
When are you gonna figure it out?
你什么时候才能明白 ?
We're not like them.
我们和他们不一样
lam nothing like you.
我跟你也不一样
Sure, you are.
当然一样
You just don't know it yet.
只是你还不知道
-What do we got? -Bar fight. Multiple knife wounds.
-什么情况 -酒吧斗殴 ， 多处刀伤
What is this, a joke? Guy's fine.
开玩笑 ? 他没事
-Where is he? -Hey, hey, don't...
-他在哪儿 ? -嘿， 别…
-l said, where is he? -I don't know who he is.
-我不知道他是谁
I can help you.
我能帮你
Six years I've been here.
我来这里六年了
No one knew me, and then you show up, and the next day she's dead!
没人知道我是堆 可你出现的第二天她就死了
I tried to warn you.
我警告过你
Why didn't you tell me it was Victor?
为什么不明说是维克多 ?
-I didn't know! -Bullshit!
-我当时不知道 -胡说 !
-Why? -l swear on my son's life, I didn't!
-为什么 ? -我以我儿子的性命发扑，我不知道 !
Victor's appetites were becoming too public.
维克多角口越来越大
I had to lock him up. He felt 1 betrayed him.
我只能把他关起来 他认为我出卖了他
Went AWOL. He said he was coming after all of us.
他竟然渔了“，他说要把我们全都于掉
You didn't come to warn me,
你不是来提醒我
you came to save your own ass.
你是来保住自己的小命
So what's your plan, Captain?
你有什么打算,队长 ?
You can't beat him, Logan, you know you can't!
罗根，你知道你打不过他
I'm gonna find him and kill him.
我会找到他的，我要杀了他
I can give you the tools to defeat him.
我有工具,可以帮你打败他
And we can still save the others.
也能救其他人的命
You mean save yourself, right?
你是说保你自己肥，是不是?
I promise you two things.
有两件事我要说明
You will suffer more pain than any other man can endure,
你要承受常人无法忍受的痛苦
but you will have your revenge.
但你会报仇雪恨
I come with you, I'm coming for blood.
我跟你走，我要报仇
No law. No code of conduct.
没有法律，没有条例
You point me in the right direction, you get the hell out of my way.
你指对方向，就给我滚一边去
When it starts, whatever the reason is that you're doing this,
一旦疼痛开始 你就专心想你做这事的原因
focus on that. Maybe it will help.
不管是什么原因，这样会有所帮助
Trust me, I've been through worse.
相信我，更糟的事我都经过
No, you haven't.
不，你没有
We're ready.
准备好了
We're gonna make you indestructible, but first we're gonna have to destroy you.
我们会让你变得刀枪不入 但首先得毁掉你
You remember what we were looking for in Africa?
你记得我们那次去非洲要找的东西吗 ?
-l remember. -Well, I found it.
-我记得 -我找到了
It helped us create a metal compound so strong
我们用它合成了一种超强的金属
that you will be able to withstand virtually anything.
可以让你承受一切攻击
It's called Adamantium.
我们称它为艾德曼金属
I can't put Victor down myself, Logan.
我赁自己灭不了维克多，罗根
To kill him, you're gonna have to embrace the other side.
想杀他，你只有拥抱自己的另一面
Become the animal.
回归又性
Let's do this.
来吧
l almost forgot.
我差点忘了
I want new ones.
我要个新的
What do you want them to say?
想要什么名字 ?
Wolverine.
金刚狼
Generals, welcome.
将军们， 欢迎
General Munson.
蒙森将军
Today we're gonna witness medical history.
今天我们将见证医学史上的奇迹
-Today we're gonna create Weapon X. -X?
-我们要制造出X武器 -X ?
Roman numeral 10.
就是罗马数字十
We are about to begin bonding Adamantium to Weapon X's skeleton.
我们要把艾德曼金属 整合到X武器的骨骼里
Let's begin.
开始吧
-We're brothers, Jimmy. -Logan!
-我们是亲兄弟， 吉米 -罗根 !
Body temperature, 108 and rising.
体温华氏1 0 8，还在升高
Why is he thrashing like that? Why isn't he sedated?
他怎么抖成这样 ? 怎么不展睡 ?
He feels pain just like the rest of us, but anesthesia won't work on him.
他能感到疼痛，麻醇剂对他不起作用
-That's why he had to volunteer. -Heart rate, 190. 195.
-所以得要他自愿 -心率190、195
-Will he survive this? -I don't know.
-他不会死肥 ? -我不知道
Son.
儿子
Heart rate well beyond maximum.
心跳超过极限
-Blood pressure? -260 over 180 and rising.
-血压呢 ? -260180，还在升
He can make it. He can make it.
他能挺过来，一定能成
Victor!
维克多 !
I love you.
我爱你
You're not an animal.
你不是动物
It means “the Wolverine”.
是“金刚狼”的意思
Well, l guess he can die.
我猜他会死
Come on, old friend. Come back.
加油 ， 老朋友，活过来
Heart rate rising.
心跳回升
Adamantium reservoir is depleted.
艾德曼金属注射完毕
No rejection. Procedure completed.
没有排蜡， 程序结束
-We did it.
-我们成功了
Yeah! Yes.
耶!
Are we taking him to the island?
我们把他带到岛上去吗 ?
The island? No.
去岛上 ? 不
The bonding works.
整合成功了
We'll use his DNA for the XI.
我们把他的D N A用到十一号上
Erase his memory.
删除他的记忆
I think he heard you.
我想他听到了
Lock down!
快关门 !
Hunt him down. Take his head off.
抓住他，把他的头割下来
Travis.
特拉维斯
-I think there's a naked man in the barn. -Yep.
-我想谷仓里有个裸男 -对
Son?
孩子?
What in hell you doing?
你在于什么 ?
-It's cold. -Cold.
-好冷
-You got no clothes on. -Yeah.
-你没穿衣服 -对
-You're not on the drugs, are you? -No.
-你没团药吧 ? -没
-No, just had a rough night. -Yeah, you could say that.
-只是昨晚不好过 -可以这么说
Come on up to the house.
进屋来吧
Some of my son's old clothes will probably fit you.
我儿子的旧衣服可能适合你
Here. Cover it up with that, huh?
先拿这个遮一下
I don't want you giving the old lady a heart attack.
我可不想让老太太犯心脏病
-You all right in there? -Yeah, yeah, I'm fine!
-你没事吧 ? -我没事
Supper's on the table.
了晚饭在桌子上
Yeah, I'll be there in a minute.
我马上来
I swear, I'm gonna pay for it.
我保证，我会赔的
-Set it down over there. -Right.
-扔在那边吧 -对
Come and sit down, son.
过来坐， 孩子
I can't thank you both enough for everything.
我不知道如何感谢你们
It wouldn't have been decent to leave you out there to freeze.
把你丢在外面冻死不太得体
-"Decent." -What?
-得体 -什么?
Nothing. I'm just not really used to that word.
没什么，我只是不怎么用那词
That's a nice chopper you've got out there.
你那辆摩托车不错
-You know motorcycles? -Oh! Lord, here we go.
-你了解摩托吗 ? -上帝 ! 又说这个了
My favorite's a '48 Panhead. Bought one new off the line.
我最喜欢 4 8 年款的 刚下线我就买了一辆
I think you're a little young for that, son.
那时候你还很小得很
You must be exhausted. You get a good night's sleep.
你一定是累坏了，得好好睡一党
In the barn.
睡谷仓肥
Nothing you can break out there.
那儿没什么可给你打碎的
Why is the moon se lonely?
月亮为什么这么孤单 ?
Why?
为什么 ?
Because she used to have a lover.
因为她普经有过爱人
He can never touch her again.
他们再也无法相拥
You sleep okay?
有睡得好吗 ?
Yeah.
不错
You look like a man fixing to do a bad thing.
你看起来要去做坏事的样子
You know what happens to men who go looking for blood?
你知道报仇的人最后的下场吗 ?
-What? -They find it.
-什么? -他们报了贫' 但也毁了自己
We all got a choice, son.
我们都有选择，孩子
-Yeah, well, mine got taken. -Bullshit.
-我的选择被于走了 -胡说
This was my son's jacket.
这是我儿子的夹克
Try it on.
试试吧
-Thank you. -Yep.
-谢谢你 -不用
You want to take my bike for a spin? Test the suspension?
你想骑我的车吗 ? 试下好不好骑
"64, huh?
6 4年款
Man, you're heavy.
你还挺沉
Yeah, I put on a little weight recently.
最近体重有点增加
-Good morning! -Good morning.
-早上好
Oh. It fits you beautifully.
你穿上挺合身
I brought you some...
我给你做了一些…
Weapon X is in the barn. He's just murdered two civilians.
义武器在谷仓里 他刚杀死了两个平民
Blow him to bits. Let's see if he can survive that.
把他炸成碎片，看他还能不能活
Come get me.
朱上我
Blow his brains all over the road!
射穿他脑袋
Damn it!
糟糕 !
Alpha one, do not lose him!
阿尔法一号，跟紧了
Alpha two! Target coming to you!
阿尔法二号， 目标朝你那边去了
Pull up!
拉起来 !
Pull back! Pull back!
升高 ! 快点!
Zero?
零号 ?
Zero, come in.
雪号, 回答
-Zero, is Logan dead? -I don't know.
-堆号，罗根死了没有? -我不知道
I'm down.
我受伤了
Zera, is he dead? Is Logan dead?
他死了没 ? 罗根死了没 ?
Zero, come in.
雪号, 回答
You tried to kill me.
你想杀我
-Logan? -Where's Victor?
-罗根 ? -维克多在哪儿 ?
Come back to base.
回基地
I'll explain everything. We'll take Victor down together.
我会解释的，我们一起于掉维克多
Wrong answer. After I kill Victor, I'm coming for you.
回答错误，杀了维克多 下一个就是你
Logan, listen to me.
了听着罗根
If you go down this road, you're not gonna like what you find.
你再这样下去，对你自己没好处
You wanted the animal, Colonel. You got it.
你想要我回归兽性，上校，你成功了
Those were good people back there. Innocent people.
他们是好人“，是无齐的
It's funny how good, innocent people tend to die around you.
真有意思 那些无境的好人总在你身边死去
Zero never stood a chance.
雪号没成功
The only thing that'll take him down is an Adamantium bullet.
只有艾德曼子弹才能制服他
This facility's compromised. Prep transport.
基地已经暴露，准备转移
Colonel, this is turning into a disaster.
上校，看来局势难以收拾
-Don't worry. We'll stop him. -Really?
-别担心，我们会阻止他 -真的吗 ?
You just spent half a billion dollars making him indestructible.
你刚花了 5 亿让他刀枪不入
-Sir? -Yes?
-<长官? -什么?
The young mutant you've been looking for. We've found him.
你要找的年轻变种人找到了
General, Logan isn't the only piece of this puzzle.
将军，罗根不是我们的唯一
I need to evacuate this facility.
必须撤离这里
Please go back to Washington. We've got work to do.
回华盛顿，我们有正事要做
Yo hablo, talk. Tu hablas, you talk.
(西班牙语 )
- El habla... Somebody translate.
谁来灵译一下
Summers!
萨黑斯 !
Sit up and take off those glasses.
坐好， 把眼镜摘下来
Then you can wear them in detention after school
那就戴着它，放学后留下来
while you write out this conjugation 100 times.
把这个词抄写1 0 0遍
-Somebody else? -He talks.
-谁来 ? -他说话
- Thank you. He talks. £f habla.
谢谢，他说话
-You sure it was Victor? -Yeah.
-你确定是维克多于的 ? -没错
Damn. I'm sorry, man.
该死，我很难过,老兄
What the hell happened to him after I left?
我离开后他到底怎么了 ?
He got worse. He felt like you abandoned him.
越来越糟，他感觉被你抛弃了
Hell, we all did.
我们都这么想
But Victor, he had to prove he was better than you.
但是维克多想证明他比你强
Hunting and killing everything he was pointed at.
他追杀了每个上校让他杀的人
Quit a few months later myself.
几个月后我也不于了
Couldn't take rounding them up.
受不了四处抓他们
-Rounding who up? -Leave it alone.
-抓堆 ? -别管了
Rounding who up, John?
抓谁，约翰 ?
Hey! Damn it, John!
可恶，约翰 !
We hunted our own kind, Logan.
我们猎杀同类，罗根
There's a special place in hell for the things we did.
我们做的事足以下十八层地狱
Mutants? Why?
变种人 ? 为什么?
Stryker said we'd be making a difference,
史崔克说我们有所不同
protecting people from the bad ones.
保护人类免受坏变种人的伤害
How are you gonna take Victor down, Logan?
你打算怎么打败维克多 ?
-Remember that stuff in Africa? -Yeah, l remember Africa. What about it?
-记得那次找的石头吗 ? -当然记得， 怎么了 ?
Damn.
天
What'd they do to you, man?
他们对你都做了什么 ?
Don't ask.
别问了
Listen, Zero said something about an island.
雪号提到过一个什么岛
Does that mean anything to you?
你知道吗 ?
Nope. But maybe Dukes knows.
不，但也许杜克斯知道
-Him and Zero were real tight. -Fred Dukes? Where is he?
-他和委号关系很好 -弗菜德杜克斯 ? 他在哪儿 ?
-He's here. -Well, let's go talk to him.
-就在此地 -找他谈谈去
Hold on. He don't get in till around 4:00.
等等，他四点名才来
But I got to warn you, he developed a bit of an eating disorder.
我可得提醒你， 他患上了饮食失调症
We all got our coping mechanisms. I'm trying to whup him back into shape.
我正试图让他恢复原形
Whatever you do, don't mention his weight.
不管你说什么都别提他的体重
Come on, Fred, if you wanna get in shape, you got to move, man.
来吧，弗莱德 要是你想有好体形，就得动起来
I told him he got to move. He's got to move! What?
我告诉过他必须得运动
Fred Dukes? That looks like the creature that ate Fred Dukes.
弗菜德杜克斯 ? 我还以为怪物把他吃了
Hey, be nice, man.
别这么说，伙计
Hey, fat... Fred.
喂，肥…弗莱德
I seem to remember that girl when she was about 85 pounds, huh?
我还记得那个 8 5 磅的女孩
Oh, that's funny. You're still so funny, Logan.
有意思，你还是那么幽默，罗根
You know where Victor is?
你知道维克多在哪儿 ?
-No idea. -What's the island, slim?
-不清楚 -那个岛叫什么 ， 瘦子 ?
Don't let the door hit you on the way out, Logan.
离这远点， 出去时别撞到门，罗根
Listen, I ain't leaving here till you tell me where Victor is.
你不告诉我维克多在哪，我就不走
So come on, bub, for old times’ sake, huh?
告诉我吧，肉球，看在过去的份上
Did you just call me Blob?
你刚才叫我肉球 ?
No, but...
不，那是…
I told you not to mention his weight. Why'd you call him Blob?
我说过别提他的体重 为什么还叫他肉球
I didn't call him Blob. I said “bub”.
我没叫他肉球，我说的是混球
-God damn it. -Hey, hey, hey. Hey, Logan.
-该死 -喂，罗根
I got an idea.
我有个办法
-This is your idea of an idea? -I'm trying to help you out, Logan.
-这就是你的和鬼主意 ? -我想帮你
Dukes don't like you that much and you know it.
可杜克斯不喜欢你
-Yeah, the feeling's mutual. -Well, use them gloves, man.
-彼此彼此 -戴上手套
Dance with him a little bit. Allow him to let his anger out on you.
和他周旋， 让他把妈火发泄到你身上
Figure if you do that, he'll probably tell you everything you want to know.
你要是让他发泄一下 他可能就告诉你一切
Come on, man, look at him.
你看他那样子
Got a big old ass coming out the front of his shirt.
大肥屁股从前面出来了
Jesus. He's gonna have a coronary, for Christ's sake.
他会得心脏病的
Is there even a stretcher big enough to take this guy out of here?
这里有抬得动他的担架吗 ?
It ain't him I'm worried about getting out of here ona stretcher.
我担心被抬出去的不是他
-You're an asshole. -Come on, Logan.
-你这缺德鬼 -你有什么本事
-Whup his ass! -You want it?
-狠接他屁股 ! -想尝尝吗 ?
Dance with him, Fred! Just like I taught you.
跟他打，弗菜德，像我教你的那样
You want to dance with me?
你想跟我打 ?
-Come on, Fred! -Oh! Oh, that feels good.
-捷他，弗莱德 ! -哦，这感觉才好
Hey! Guess what?
怎么样 ?
See, he gonna talk now.
这下他必须和你谈谈了
-You got him right where you want him. -Whose side are you on, anyway?
-你想让他怎样就怎样 -你小子和谁一边 ?
Come on!
来呀 !
Come on, now, lamb chop!
来呀，羊排
Damn!
糟糕 !
Now, where's Victor?
现在说吧，维克多在哪儿
Little dark for sunglasses, don't you think?
戴着太阳镜有点暗是吗 ?
-Please, don't! Please, don't! -Victor!
-求你了 不要 -维克多 !
Hey, hey! Where's Victor?
维克多在哪儿 ?
Yeah. Victor's with Stryker on the island.
他和史崔克在岛上
They run it together.
他们一起做试验
What? They what? Victor will be with Stryker?
什么 ? 维克多和史崔克是一伙的 ?
Yeah.
是的
You didn't know that?
你不知道吗 ?
All that's left now is Logan. I trust you can handle that.
现在只剩罗根了 我相信你能应付得了
-I did before, didn't 1? -Oh, yes. You did that.
-我之前赢过他，不是吗 ? -哦，对，你赢过他
Our deal. It still applies, right?
我们的协议， 还算数吧 ?
Of course. Now bag him and tag him, Captain.
当然，现在把他打包贴上标签，队长
What's the island?
什么岛?
It's where Stryker takes them after Victor's caught them.
史崔克让维克多捉人 然后把他们关在岛上
Wait, hang on a minute. Takes who?
等会儿，抓谁去 ?
Mutants.
变种人
Rumor is that Stryker's doing experiments on them there.
据说是史崔克用他们做实验
I mean, you never wondered what happened to them?
你从没想过他们会怎样 ?
I tried not to.
我尽力不去想
They killed her so I'd let them put Adamantium in me.
他们杀了她 只是为了让我接受艾德曼金属的注入
They killed her for a goddamn experiment.
只不过为了一个该死的实验
-Where is it? Where is it? -Logan, Stryker kept it real secret.
-在哪儿 ? -史崔克不可能告诉我的
But a prisoner escaped there once.
但是， 有人逃出来过
-Who? -His name was Remy LeBeau.
-谁?
He was a street hustler from New Orleans.
新奥尔良一个街头赌客
The guards at the prison called him Gambit
监狱的看守叫他千王
because he kept taking all their money at poker.
因为他赌博赢光了他们的钱
-That's all I know. -What's Stryker up to, Fred?
-我就知道这么多 -史崔克做什么试验 ?
What's the endgame?
他有什么最终目的
He's taking their powers. Trying to combine them somehow.
获得他们的超能力，再设法整合起来
That's all l know, Logan. That's all Il know.
我只知道这么多，罗根， 就这些
If I have to come back here, I'm gonna take your head off.
如果你骗我，我就把你的头割下来
I'm coming with you, Logan.
一起去吧，罗根
-There's no redemption where I'm going. -l ain't asking.
-我去的地方是没有回头路的 -那当然
There's our dude.
那是我们的伙计
That's cool.
真酷
I'm gonna go cover the back in case he rabbits.
我来看守后门以防他溜走
-I'm not gonna fight with him. -Yeah, right.
-我没打算和他打架 -是么
What? I get in fights with everybody?
怎么， 我跟每个人都得打架吗 ?
Don't dogs kill cats?
狗不是爱咬猫的吗 ?
Just go cover the back, will you?
那替我盯着后面
-Give me 500. -I'm in.
-给我五百块 -我也玩
Are you Remy LeBeau?
你是雷米勒博吗 ?
-Do l owe you money? -No.
-我不欠你钱吧 ? -不
Then Remy LeBeau I am.
那我就是雷米勒博
Large blind's 100. Small blind's 50.
大注一百，小注五十
-May I deal you in? -What can I get for 17 bucks?
-我给你发牌吧 ? -十七块，能玩什么 ?
$17?
十七块?
A cab ride home, perhaps?
打车回家大概够了
You my brother's new babysitter, John?
你当我兄弟的新保姆吗， 约翰 ?
l ain't Bradley, Victor.
我可不是布菜德利
And your creepy black coat don't scare me.
你吓不到我
Really?
是吗 ?
Worked on Dukes.
对杜克斯挺管用的
You shouldn't have done that, ‘cause now I'm gonna kill you
你真不该那么做 我要在罗根下手之前
before Logan even gets a chance.
先杀了你
So what brings you to our fair city, sir?
哪阵风把你吹来的， 先生 ?
Victor Creed.
维克多克里德
And who's that?
他是谁 ?
The man I'm gonna kill.
我要杀的人
He works with a man named Stryker on an island.
给岛上一个叫史崔克的人于活
-Just need to know where it is. -And why would you think I know that?
-我想知道在哪儿 -为什么你认为我知道 ?
Well, ‘cause I know who you are, Gambit.
因为我知道你是谁，千王
You're the guy who escaped and you're the guy who's gonna take me back there.
你光出来了，就能带我回那儿
You know, John, there's something l always wanted to tell you.
知道吗，约翰 有些事我一直想告诉你
You're predictable.
你是可以预知的
I can feel your spine, Johnny Boy.
我能摸到你的背梁骨
That's funny. Never knew you had one.
真有趣，我原以为你没有呢
Those are mighty nice tags you have on there, sir.
你戴着牌子， 先生
The men who took me wore tags just like them.
抓我的人戴着一模一样的牌子
Hey, now, bub, you listen to me.
听我说，伙计
Damn it. That little...
该死，那小…
Two years I rotted in that hellhole and I ain't never going back.
我在那鬼地方受了两年罪 我可不回去
Shiny.
真亮
Tell me something, Jimmy.
告诉我，吉米
Do you even know how to kill me?
你知道怎么能杀了我吗 ?
I'm gonna cut your goddamned head off.
我要把你该死的脑袋割下来
See if that works.
看能不能杀死你
You're getting slow, old man.
你反应迟钝了，老兄
You son of a bitch.
狗杂种
You're gonna die for what you did to her.
你杀了她，就别想活
Victor!
维克多 !
Well, that's a nice stick.
哦，拐棍儿挺不错
Okay, shithead, here's the deal.
听着，蠢货，这样如何
See, you're gonna take me to this island, where I can kill Creed, Stryker
你带我去那个岛 我来杀了克里德和史峙克
and pretty much everyone you hate in this world. Do you understand?
和那些你恨之入骨的家伙
You're really gonna kill them?
你真会守了他们 ?
As long as you stay out of my way, yeah.
只要你识趣点
Colonel?
上校?
-General? -Is this Weapon XI?
-将军? -这是十一号武器吗 ?
All their strengths and none of their weaknesses.
只有他们的优点，没有弱点
You really hate them, don't you?
你非常恨他们，是不是 ?
No, I don't hate them.
不:我不恨他们
After 20 years of working with mutants, I just know what they can do.
和他们一起2 0年 我知道他们的能力
We can win this war before it starts and save countless lives in the process.
战争没开始我们就能获胜 拯救无数生命
Pre-emptive action is the only action here, General.
我们只是先发制人， 将军
The days of our country sitting on the sidelines are over.
我们国家碌碌无为的日子结束了
We need to take the fight to the enemy before they take the fight to us.
我们要在他们开火前先解决掉他们
-l admire your passion, I do. -Thank you.
-我很欣赏你的激情
But this is as far as it goes.
不过先到此为止
-Weapon X was a hiccup. -We know about your son, Bill.
-X武器是个小失误 -我们知道你的儿子，比尔
We know he's a mutant, and we know he killed your wife.
他也是变种人，他杀了你妻子
-You shouldn't have kept that from us. -That...
-你不应该对我们隐瞒
That has nothing to do with my work, General.
那些和我的工作无关
Bullshit.
胡说
You're too close to this. I'm shutting you down.
你陷得太深了“，我要停止你的试验
Okay. You're right. I won't lie to you.
你是对的，我不该对你说谎
My son did bring the problem home for me,
的确是我的儿子把我弄到这步田地的
but I took an oath
但我也立过暂
to protect the American people
要保护美国公民
from every threat, both foreign
不受任何外来的
and domestic.
和本国的威胁
-You don't like flying, huh? -I'm fine.
-你不喜欢飞行， 是吗 ?
-Just concentrate on what you're doing. -You sure?
-专心点 -你确定 ?
You got a bit of sweat on your brow there.
你额头都出汗了
Very funny. Just keep your eyes on the...
真好笑， 专心看…
On the what? The clouds? Keep my eyes on the clouds?
看什么 ? 看云彩 ?
You're up and down like a freaking yo-yo here!
你开得像个悠悠球似的 !
-Where'd you get this thing, anyway? -Oh, this is my baby.
-从哪弄的破玩意儿? -这可是我的宝贡
I won her in a game. Jacks over fives.
我玩牌赢的
Great.
真是棒极了
Relax. We're almost there.
放松点，我们快到了
There it is. The island. Three Mile Island.
到了“，就是这个岛，三里岛
Hiding in plain sight.
就在人们眼皮底下
No one's gonna snoop around a nuclear reactor.
没人想要靠近核反应堆
They think it's gonna turn them into freaks.
他们以为会变成怪物
-Like you? -Right.
-像你这样的 ? -没错
All right. You ready? Because it's now or never. Let's go.
准备好了吗 ? 机不可失' 行动吧
About time.
刚刚好
Hey, if it makes you feel any better, this is really gonna hurt.
这样你感觉好些，跳下去肯定疼
Well, yeah, it kind of does, actually.
实际上是感党好些
-Good luck. -Likewise.
-祝你好运 -你也是
Oh, shit.
妈的
How you doing? Everything all right?
怎么样了 ? 没事吧 ?
-Is he ready yet? -A few more hours.
-他还要多久 ? -几个小时
-And he will respond to my commands? -Absolutely.
-他会听我命令吧 ? -绝对听
Logan.
罗根
Welcome back to the war.
欢迎回到战场
Before I gut you, I want to know why.
趁我还没杀你，我得问问为什么
I needed your powers for the Pool.
我要把你们的能力给死侍
-For the what? -The mutant killer.
-给什么 ? -变种人杀手
Deadpool.
死侍
Years of searching and refining,
这么多年的研究和改善
finding the right powers that can coexist in one body
就是为了找到能共存于一身
without ripping it apart.
而不会互相抵触的能力
My son was the first piece of the puzzle.
我儿子就是第一个贡献者
Logan, you were the last.
罗根， 你是最后一个
You made Weapon XI possible.
你使得十一号武器成为可能
l asked you to help, but you said you wanted the quiet life.
我想得到你的帮助 可你只要平静的生活
Well,
那好吧
I've learned that nothing motivates the men in your family like revenge.
我知道对于你们家的人来说 只有报仇才能成为动力
Who are you?
你是谁 ?
Oh, she's real, old friend.
她是真实的，老朋友
Did you really think we'd just let you walk away?
你真以为我们就这样放过你了吗 ?
You're a dangerous man.
你是危险人物
We like to keep an eye on dangerous men.
我们会盯紧你这种危险人物的
Tell him about the day you died.
告诉他你死那天发生的事
They gave me a shot of hydrochlorothiazide.
他们给我打了一针镇静剂
It reduces the heart rate so low it appears you flatlined.
让我心跳极慢，看起来像死了一样
Don't be angry with her.
别生她的气
She's a real credit to your species.
在你们同类中，她算了不起了
Did you know that her sister has diamond-hard skin?
她妹妹的皮肤跟钻石一样硬
Kayla's mutation is tactohypnosis.
凯拉的能力是触碰催眼
She can influence people as long as she touches them.
她只要一碰就能控制人们的思想
Quite a useful tool in a seduction.
是引诱别人的有效工具
It was never real, my friend.
你们的爱情不是真的，朋友
It was real for me.
对我来说是真的
I told you if you came down this road, you wouldn't like what you found.
我说过别继续下去，你只会失望
That story you told me about a man who gets flowers for the moon,
你说的那个 为月亮摘玫瑰的男人的故事
l had it backwards.
我把它演绎成
I thought you were the moon and I was your wolverine.
你是月亮，我是你的金刚狼
But you're the trickster, aren't you?
其实你是崔斯特，对吗 ?
I'm just the fool who got played.
我只是个被玩弄的白痴
The worst part of it is, I should have known.
最傻的是，我应该早知道的
But l ignored my instincts.
但我忽视了我的直觉
lignored what I really am.
忽视了真实的我
But that won't ever happen again.
再也不会发生这种事了
-Colonel? -Not now, Kayla.
-上校? -现在不行， 凯拉
I've done everything you've asked.
你吟只的我都照做了
My sister.
我妹妹
You said if 1 helped you, you'd let her go.
你说过，只要我帮你， 你就会放了她
Kayla, it's not as simple as that. Her mutation is unique. Quite beautiful.
没那么简单 她的变异是独特的， 非常棒
We just need a little more time to analyze it, that's all.
我们需要多点时间再研究一下
You let him go?
你让他走了 ?
-Victor, please. -You can't let him go.
-维克多 -你不能放他走
-You can't beat him, Victor. -Then give me the Adamantium!
-你打不过他 -给我也注入艾德曼金属 !
-Your tests came back. -We had a deal!
-你的实验结果出来了 -我们说好的
You would never survive the operation.
手术会让你死的
-l can take anything he can. -No, you can't.
-他能做到的，我也能 -你不能
You're my favorite soldier, Victor. Be patient. Your time will come.
你是我最得意的人，维克多 耐心点，会轮到你的
He's using us.
他在利用我们
How about this time you die for real?
这次真死一次怎么样
Let me go.
放了我
Your little mind games don't work on me.
你这招对我不管用
Victor!
维克多 !
Feels good, doesn't it?
感觉不错吧
All that rage.
看你狂怒的样子
-Do it. -Logan!
-杀了我 -罗根
-You're not an animal. -Oh, yes, you are.
-你不是动物 -你就是动物
Do it.
来啊
Finish it.
报仇吧
Logan?
罗根 ?
My sister. They have my sister.
我妹妹，他们抓了我妹妹
Please. I didn't trick you into loving me.
对不起，我不是利用超能让你爱我
It was real for me, too.
我也真的爱你
Please, I'm so sorry. They have my sister.
真的对不起，他们带走了我妹妹
Where is she?
她在哪儿 ?
-Activate Weapon XI! -The bonding process isn't complete.
-启动十一号武器 -整合还没完成
Just do it! Now!
快点' 就现在 !
Come on. Come on!
跟我走 !
Okay.
好吧
Perfect.
太好了
-Kayla, get these kids out of here. -Logan...
-凯拉，带孩子们离开这里
Find another way out.
另找个出口
Okay. Let's go.
好 我们走
Wade, is that you?
韦德，是你吗 ?
Guess Stryker finally figured out how to shut you up.
史崔克终于知道怎么让你闭嘴了
Now...
现在…
Wade?
直德 ?
You don't have to do this.
你没必要这样做
All right, maybe you do.
看来你必须这样
You're shitting me.
你在开我玩笑
Shoot on sight!
射击
-I can help! Point me at them! -Go.
-我能帮上忙 ! 让我去吧 ! -去吧
Go! Now!
现在 !
-Did I get them? -Yeah.
-我打中了吗 ? -对
-Let's go. -I can't go.
-我们走肥 -我不能
-Kayla, come on! -l have to stay here.
-凯拉 ! -我得留下来
You take them.
你带他们走
Go! Go!
快 1快走!
Go left.
走左边
Left.
左边
-What? -We go left.
-什么? -我们往左走
-You can't see. -Trust me.
-你根本看不见 -相信我
Let's see you dance up here.
让我看你打
Nobody kills you but me.
除了我谁也别想杀你
Back to back!
背靠背 !
-I got him! -Oh, no, you don't.
-我看到他了 ! -你没有
Stop! This can't be the way.
停 ! 不可能是这边
-This is the way. -How do you know?
-就是这边 -你怎么知道
I just know. Come on.
我就是知道，来吧
Adamantium bullets.
艾德曼金属子弹
Let's see him heal with a few of these through his thick skull.
看看子弹穿过他厚脑袋壳的反应
You can't stop him, even with that.
你杀不了他，就算用那个也不行
-He'll heal. -His brain may heal,
-他能愈合 -他的大脑也许会愈合
but his memories won't grow back.
但那些记忆回不去了
This doesn't change anything between us, Victor.
这改变不了我们之间的关系，维克多
-We're done. -We can never be done, Jimmy.
-我们之间完了 -不会完的，吉米
We're brothers, and brothers look out for each other.
我们是兄弟，兄弟会并肩作战
-You miss me? -Ah, Jesus.
-想我了吧 ? -上帝
You know, when you said you were gonna kill everyone,
你说要把他们都杀光的时候
I thought you may just have been exaggerating.
我以为你就吹吹牛虹了
Yeah.
了风
Do I look like a man who exaggerates?
我看起来像吹牛的吗 ?
-You're welcome. -Logan?
-别客气 -罗根 ?
Logan.
罗根
There's kids trying to get off the island. Split up. Go!
一些孩子想离开这个岛，分头走 !
I'm on it.
这事我处理
Kayla! Kayla!
如拉 !
Hey.
嘿
I love you.
我爱你
-Hey... -I'm so cold.
-我很冷
Listen to me. I'm gonna get you out of here.
我会带你离开这儿
Understand?
明白吗 ?
Just go easy. Nice and easy. That's it. That's it.
小心 ， 慢点，我们走
Okay. I'm gonna get you help.
我去找人来帮你
Logan!
罗根 !
I should make you pull the trigger.
我能让你扣动扳机
But that would make us no better than you.
但那让我和你一样坏了
Throw the gun away.
把枪扔掉
Turn around.
转过身去
Walk until your feet bleed. And then keep walking.
走吧， 一直走，别停下
ft will be all right, Scott.
会没事的，斯考特
My name is Charles Xavier.
我是谢维查尔斯
I'm a mutant like you.
我跟你们一样是变种人
-l can hear your thoughts. -Yes, and can hear yours.
-我能听到你的思想 -我也能听到你们的
You're safe now. Come. We have to go.
你们没事了“，来吧' 我们走
Come on, let's go.
快，我们走吧
The kids are safe.
孩子们安全了
Damn.
该死
-Who are you? -What do you mean, who am I?
-你是谁 ? -你什么意思 ' 我是谁 ?
I'm the guy who brought you here. Now, we got to go.
我带你来的，现在我要带你走
Where the hell am I?
我到底在哪里?
Listen to me. I'm a friend.
听好了“， 我是你的朋友
-I'm a friend. -Yeah? What's my name?
-我是你朋友 -是吗 ? 我叫什么名字 ?
-What's my name? -Your name is Logan.
-我叫什么 ? -你叫罗根
You need to trust me. We have to go.
你得相信我，我们走吧
Follow me.
跟我走
Now!
现在 !
Do you know her?
你认识她 ?
No.
不认识
Hey, these boys aren't gonna like what you've done to this place.
他们肯定不高兴看到你搞成这样
We really need to go.
我们真得走了
I'll find my own way.
我自己会走的
Good luck.
祝好运
Colonel Stryker?
史赃克上校 ?
-Colonel William Stryker? -Yes.
-威廉史崔克上校 ? -是我
You're wanted for questioning in connection with the death
由于你与蒙森将军的死有关
of General Munson, sir.
你将接受审讯，先生
Another.
再来一杯
You're American?
你是美国人吗 ?
Canadian, I think.
加拿大人“，我想是
Are you drinking to forget?
你在借酒消悉吗 ?
No, I'm drinking to remember.
不 ' 我喝酒是为了回忆